Guide to the Isaac Levi Papers, 1949-2014 ASP.2016.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Correspondence, 1949-2014; I.
  - Alphabetical Correspondence, 1949-2014; 1.
    - Marcus, Ruth B., 1990 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Marcus, Ruth, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Marschak, Jacob, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Matilal, Bimal Krishna, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Maxwell, Grover, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - May, Kenneth, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - McClellan, Edward F., 1971-1976 (Box 10, Folder 22-23)
    - McClellan, Edward F., 1981-2001 (Box 10, Folder 24-25)
    - McDowell, John, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - McLaughlin, Andrew, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Meeden, Glenn, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Meehl, Paul E., 1990-1993 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Meginnis, James R., 1978 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Meinong, A., undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Melitz, Jaques, c. 1960s (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Mellor, H.D., 1988-1997 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Mellor, H.D., c. 1960s-1980s (Box 10, Folder 34-36)
    - Melman, Seymour, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Menaker, Walter, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Mercer/Sleigh on Leibniz, 1983-1993 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Merill, Gary H., 1977 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Merin, Arthur, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Merritt, Robert L., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Merritt, Robert L., 1980-1985 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Mesak, Cheryl, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Michael, Michaelis, undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Michalos, Alex C., 1964 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Miller, David, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Miller, David on Gambling With Truth, 1971-1980 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Miller, David, 1972-1990 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Miller, David: Miller's Paradox, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Minnameier, Gerald, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Moganbesser, Sidney, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Morgenbesser, Sydney, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Morton, Newton E., 1955-1967 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Mothersill, Mary, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Nagel, Ernest, 1979-1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Nagel, Ernest, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH), 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH), 1987 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - National Science Foundation, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - National Science Foundation Application, November 22, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - National Science Foundation Research, 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - National Science Foundation, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - National Science Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Nelson, R.J., Behaviorism is False, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Nelson, R.J., Machines, undated (Box 11, Folder 16-17)
    - Nelson, R.J., undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Nelson, R.J., Sorting Algorithms, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Nelson, Ray, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Nersessian, Nancy, 1981-1986 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Newman, Fred, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Neyman, Jerzy, c. 1970s (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Neyman, Jerzy and ES Pearson, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Nicholas, J.M., 1983 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Niiniluoto, Ilkka, 1976-1993 (Box 11, Folder 26-27)
    - Niiniluoto, Ilkka, 1982-1985 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Niiniluoto, Ilkka, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Nittka, Alexander, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Norton, John D., 2003 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Nozick, Robert, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Nozick, Robert, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - O'Connor, John, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Oliver, Alex, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Olsson, Erik J., 2003 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Olsson, Erik J., 2006 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Olsson, Frank, 1999-2004 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Olsson, Frank, 199-2004 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Papineau, David, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Parikh, Rohit, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Parsons, Charles, 1979-1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Parsons, Charles, c. 1960s (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Parsons, Charles, c. 1980s (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Pearson, E.S. and C.J. Clopper, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Pearson, E.S., 1961 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Petit, Phillip, c. 1980s (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Phelps, Edmund, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Picardi, Eva, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Pierce notes and Reviews, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Pietarinen, Juhani, 1967-1978 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Piller, Christian, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Pilpel, Avital, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Pior, A.N., 1962 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Pitowsky, Itamar, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Pitowsky, Itamar, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Plott & Grether, etc., c. 1982 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Polger, Steven, c. 1970s (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Pollock, John, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Popper, Karl R., undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Putnam, Hilary, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Rabin, Michael O., undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Rabinowicz, Wlodzimierz, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Raiffa, Howard, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Ramsey, F., undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Rapaport, Elizabeth, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Rapoport, Anatol, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Rasch, Dieter, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Ray, Paramesh, undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Rejwan, Nissim, 1967-1971 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Renwick, James H., 1963-1968 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Richter, Reed, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Riepe, Dale and John Somerville, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Rimscha, M.V., 1983 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Risse, Mathias, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Rochester, N., 1953-1955 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Roemer, John E., 1985 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Rogers (Notes on…), undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Roitblat, H.L., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Roorda, Jonathan, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Rosenberg, Jay F., undated (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Rosenkrantz, Roger, c. 1970s (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Rosenthal, David M., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Rosow, Irving, c. 1960s (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Rott, Hans, 1980-2000 (Box 12, Folder 47-50)
    - Rovane, Carol, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Rovane, Carol, c. 1990s (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
    - Rowan, Michael, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Runnals, A.R., 1978 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Rustin, Bayard, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Sakharov, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Salmon, Wendy, c. 1960s-1970s (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Samuelson, Paul A., c. 1950s (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Sandqvist, Tor., 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Sanford, David, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Sarndal, Carl E., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Savage, L.J., c. 1960s-1970s (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Savage, L.J., Ward Edwards and Harold Lindman, c. 1960s (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Schaffner, Kenneth, c. 1960s (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Scheffler, Israel, c. 1960s-1980s (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Schick, Fred, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Schlesinger, G., c. 1970s (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Schlick, Moritz, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Schrag, Daniel, 1964-1989 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Schulte, Oliver, 1999-2002 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Schurz, Gerhard, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Schwartz, David, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Schwartz, Robert, c. 1970s (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Schwartz, Thomas, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Scott, Tom, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Segerberger, Krister, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Sellars, Wilfrid, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Sen, Amartya, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 29-30)
    - Settle, Thomas B., 1983 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Shackel, G.L.S., 1962-1966 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Shafer, Glenn, 1977-1983 (Box 13, Folder 33-35)
    - Shapere, Dudley, c. 1960s (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
    - Shapere, Dudley, c. 1970s (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Shapiro, Herman, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Shawson, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Sheynin, O.B., c. 1970s (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Shier, Ju, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Shimony, Abner, c. 1980s (Box 14, Folder 8-10)
    - Shu Li, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Shuman, S.I., 1970 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Shumeli, Effraim, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Sieg, Wilfred, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Simon, Herbert, c. 1960s (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Simon, Walter, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Sinnot-Armstrong, Walter, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Sinnott-Armstrong, Walter, 1991, 2006-2007 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Sintonen, Matti, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Sklar, Lawrence, 1967-1973 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Skyrms, Brian, 1983-1994 (Box 14, Folder 21-22)
    - Skyrms, Brian, c. 1990s (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Smart, J.J.C., John Leslie and Ian Hacking, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Smith, C.A.B., c. 1960s (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Smith, Peter, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Smokler, Howard, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Sneed, Joseph D., 1966-1979 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Sober, Elliot, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Sommers, Fred, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Sorensen, Roy A., 1984 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Spector, Marshall, undated (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Spielman, Steven, c. 1970s (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
    - Spock Benjamin Case, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Spohn, Wolfgang, 1985-2001 (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
    - Steenbergen and Lavine, c. 2001 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Stein, Howard on Poincare, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Stein, Howard, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Stein, Howard, c. 1970s-1980s (Box 15, Folder 9-11)
    - Stein, Howard, c. 1980s (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Steiner, Mark, 1976-1982 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Stemmer, Nathan, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Stone, M., 1969 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Stove, D., 1969 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Strasnick, Steven, c. 1970s-1980s (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Strasnick, Steven, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Sudderth, William D., undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Suppes, Patrick, 1963-1992 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Sussman, Marvin B. and Marie R. Huag, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Swain, Marshall B., 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Swanson, Eric, undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Swijtink, Zeno G., undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Takeuti, Gaisi, undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Tannsjo, Torbjorn, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Taylor, Richard, undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Teitelman, Michael, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Teller, Paul, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Tichy, P., undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Tillman, F., undated (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Tornebohm, Hakan, undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Travel Correspondence and Documentation, c.1970s-1980s (Box 15, Folder 33-34)
    - Travel Correspondence, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Tukey, John W., 1960 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Tuomela, Raimo, c. 1970s (Box 16, Folder 3-4)
    - Tversky, Amos, 1974-1994 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Van Fraasen, Bas C., 1977 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Van Fraasen, Bas C., 1978-1981 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Van Fraasen, Bas C., 1986 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Van Fraasen, Bas C., Comment on "Belief and the Will" by Levi, 1983-1989 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Vapnik,Vladimir, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Varzi, Achille C., 1996 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Vetter, Herman, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Vickers, Jack, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Vickers, John, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Von Plato, Jan, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Von Plato, Jan, 1983-1991 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Von Plato, Jan, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Von Plato, Jan, 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Von Plato, Jan, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Wagner, Carl, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Wakker, Peter, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Wakker, Peter, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Wald, Abraham., c. 1940s (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Waldner, Ilmar, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Wallace, John R., 1967 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Wallace, John R., 1970 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Wallace, John R., c. 1960s (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Wallace, John R., undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Walley, Peter (Royal Statistical Society), 1995 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Wartofsky, Marx W., 1991 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Watanabe, Satosi, c. 1960s (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Watkins, J.W., c. 1960s (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Weatherson, undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Weber, Elke, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Weiner, Joan, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Weinstein, Scott, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Weirich, Paul, 1983-1986 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Weirich, Paul, c. 2004 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Welty, Gordon, and Cliff Lloyd, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - White, Michael J., 1979 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Whiteside, D.T., 1970 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Will, Fredrick L., 1969 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Williams, P.M., 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Williamson, Timothy, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Wilson, Edwin B., undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Wilson, Margaret, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Winsberg, Eric, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Wolfowitz, Jacob, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Wolfson College, Cambridge Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Wright, Crispin, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Yaari, Menahem, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Yalcin, Seth, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Yourhrau, Palle, 1982-1985 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Zabludowski, A., undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Zadeh, L.A., 1976-1984 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Zanstra, Herman, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Zellner, Arnold, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Zellner, Arnold, 1981-1986 (Box 17, Folder 24-25)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1955-1992; 2.
    Subseries 2. Chronological Correspondence contains scholarly and professional correspondence files kept by Levi and organized by year.
    - Correspondence, 1955-1960 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 31-32)
    - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 33-34)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, 1967 (September) (Box 17, Folder 36-37)
    - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 39-41)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (July) (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (July-August) (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (January) (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (September) (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 46-48)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 2-4)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Fall, Spring) (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 7-8)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1977 (Summer) (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 12-13)
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 14-16)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 20-23)
    - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 24-25)
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 15-16)
    - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 17-20)
    - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 2003-2008 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, July, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Probability and Decision Theory Correspondence, c. 1950s-2007; 3.
    Subseries 3. Probability and Decision Theory Correspondence contains scholarly and professional correspondence files kept by Levi concerned chiefly with the relevance of probability and decision theory to scientific inference. Files are organized alphabetically by last name.
    - Albin, Peter, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Alchourron, Carlos E., undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Anscombe, F.J. and Robert Auman, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Arrow, Kenneth J., undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Articles (Assorted), 1992 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Atkinson, Anthony B., 1979 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Aumann, Robert "Agreeing to Disagree", 1976-1994 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Aumann, Robert and M Machsler, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Aumann, Robert J., on Common Knowledge, 1974-1998 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Aumann, Robert, 1974-1987 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Bacharach, Michael, 1985-1992 (Box 20, Folder 16-17)
    - Bacharach, Michael, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Balch, M, Peter Fisburn et al., undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Bandopadhyay, Tardas, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Bandyopahaya, Prasanta S., 1994 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Barbera, Salvador and Pattanaik, Prasanta K., 1986 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Basset Jr., Gilbert W., 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Becker, Gordon M. and Charles G. McClintock, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Belief Revision, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Bell, David E., 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Bernheim, Douglas, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Besley, Tim, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Binmore, Ken, 1987-1993 (Box 20, Folder 29-31)
    - Blackorby, Nissen, Primont and Russell, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Bloom, David E., 1984-1987 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Bochman, Alexander, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Boutilier, Craig, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Brams, Steven J., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Broome, John., 1984 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Bryant, John, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Buchanan, James M., 1964 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Budescu, David V., 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Cantwell, John, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Chichilinsky, Graciela, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Cohen, Michelle and Jean-Yves Jaffray, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Comments on Newcombe, c. 1970s (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Contraction, c. 1980s (Box 21, Folder 4-5)
    - Cubitt, Robin P., 1993-1996 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - D'Aspremont, Claude, Louis Gevers and Peter J. Hammond, 1974-1979 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Dasgupta, Partha, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Dasgupta, Partha, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Dawes, Robyn M., 1991 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Dawes, Robyn M., 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Dekel, Eddie, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Dreze, Jacques H. and Kenneth J. Arrow, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Edgington, Dorothy, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Einhorn, Hillel J. and Robin M. Hogarth, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Etherington, David, Robert C. Moore, Kurt Konolidge and Hector J. Levesque, 1980s-1990s (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Farhi, Edward and Jeffrey Goldstone, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Farinas del Cerro and Andreas Herzig, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Ferrante, Vittorioemanuele, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Fischoff, Baruch, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Fishburn, Peter, c. 1980s (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Freedman, David A. and Roger Purves, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Friedman, Nir and Joseph Y. Halpern, undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Fuhrman, Andre, 1990-1994 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Gardenfors, Peter, 1977-2007 (Box 21, Folder 25-29)
    - Geanakoplos, John, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Gigerenze, Gerd, 1987-1989 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Gilboa, Itzhak and David Schmeidler, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Gilboa, Itzhak, 1987-1994 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
    - Glaister, Stephen M., 1997 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Glymour, Clark, Richard Scheines et al., c. 1990s (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Goldman, A., 1994 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Green, Edward, 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Groenendjik, Jeronen and Martin Stokhof, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Grove, Adam, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Halpern, Fagin, et.al, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Hammond, Peter (non-Archimedean Probabilities), 1992 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Hammond, Peter, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Hansson, Sven Ove, c. 1990-2000 (Box 22, Folder 12-13)
    - Harsanyi, John C., 1978-1983 (Box 22, Folder 14-15)
    - Harsanyi, John C., 1986-1989 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Hild, Matthias, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Hograth, Robin M., 1975 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Humberstone, I.L., 1986 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Hyun Song Shin, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Independence and Dominance, undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Johnsen, Thore H. and John B. Donaldson, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Jones-Lee, M.W., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Kahneman, Daniel and Amos Tversky (Prospect Theory), c. 1980s (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Kahneman, Daniel and Amos Tversky, c. 1970s (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Kahneman, Daniel and Amos Tversky, c. 1980s (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Kantor, Paul B and Newcombe, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Karni, Edi, David Schmeidler, and Karl Vind, undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Kelly, Kevin, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Klemisch-Ahlert, Marlies, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Koslow, Arnold, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Kreps, David M. and Robert Wilson, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Kyburg, Henry E., 1990-1995 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Kyburg, Henry E., Combinatorial Semantics, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Lamarre, Phillipe and Yoaz Shoham, undated (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Lehmann, Daniel and Freund, Michael, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Lehmann, Daniel, Kraus, Sarit and Magidor, Menachem, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Lichtenstein, Sarah and Paul Slovic, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Lindley, Tversky and Brown, c. 1970s-1980s (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Lindstrom, Sten, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Lipman, Barton L., 1992 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Loomes, Graham and Robert Sugden, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Loui, Ron P., 1992 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Luce, R. Duncan and David H. Krantz, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Machina, Mark J., 1981-1986 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Machina, Mark J., 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Malinvaud, E., 1979 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Malkiel, Burton G., 1982 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Margalit, Avishai and Menahem Yaari, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Maskin, Eric, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - McClellan, Edward F., 1994 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Menahem, Yaari, 1985-1987 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Meyer, Thomas A., 1998 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Mongin, Phillip and Edi Karni, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Mongin, Phillip, 1996-1998 (Box 23, Folder 14-15)
    - Morreau, Michael, 1995-1998 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Mundici, Daniele, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Narveson, Jan and Michael Webster on Newcombe, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Nau, Robert F., 1991 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Nayak, Abhaya C., 1991-1993 (Box 23, Folder 20-21)
    - Nehrig, Klaus, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Newcombe's Many Problems, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Nida-Rumelin, Julian, undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - O'Flaherty Brendan, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 25)